Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG.37.4
New York University Archives
- Series III: Audio Recordings, 67170
  - Subseries B: 1/4 Inch Reels (3 3/4 IPS), 67143
    - Auden Festival: Symposium on "Auden's Legacy" I, 20-Oct-83; cuid4335; 180974; 1 sound tape reels (Box 76, Folder 24, Box Access 7, Item 15, Item 16)
      Participants include Christopher Isherwood, J.D. McClatchy, Dr. Ursula Niebuhr, Sir Stephen Spender, and Edward Mendleson as moderator.
      Tape 1 of 3 from this event. Tapes for this event are in Box 75, Folders 24-26.
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 7:15 & ACCESS 7:16
      Spender, Stephen, 1909-1995; Isherwood, Christopher, 1904-1986; Niebuhr, Ursula; McClatchy, J.D., 1945-; Mendelson, Edward
    - Auden Festival: Symposium on "Auden's Legacy" II, 20-Oct-83; cuid4336; 180975; 1 sound tape reels (Box 76, Folder 25, Box Access 7, Item 17)
      Tape 2 of 3 from this event.Tapes for this event are in Box 75, Folders 24-26.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:17
      Mendelson, Edward; Spender, Stephen, 1909-1995; McClatchy, J.D., 1945-; Niebuhr, Ursula; Isherwood, Christopher, 1904-1986
    - Auden Festival: Symposium on "Auden's Legacy" III, 20-Oct-83; cuid4337; 180976; 1 sound tape reels (Box 76, Folder 26, Box Access 7, Item 18)
      Participants include Christopher Isherwood, J.D. McClatchy, Dr. Ursula Niebuhr, Sir Stephen Spender, and Edward Mendelson as moderator.
      Tape 3 of 3 from this event. Tapes for this event are in Box 75, Folders 24-26.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:18
      Isherwood, Christopher, 1904-1986; Niebuhr, Ursula; Mendelson, Edward; McClatchy, J.D., 1945-; Spender, Stephen, 1909-1995
    - Roland Barthes Festival: "Barthes and the Visual Arts" Round table discussion with Dore AShton, Richard Avedon, Annette Michelson, Richard Sennett, Edmund White Tape I, 18-May-84; cuid4338; 180879 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: "Barthes and the Visual Arts" Roundtable discussion with Dore Ashton, Richard Avedon, Annette Michelson, Richard Sennett, Edmund White Tape II, 19-May-84; cuid4339; 180880 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Breyten Breytenbach "The Writer in Totalitarian Countries" I, 6-Feb-85; cuid4340; 180938 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Breyten Breytenbach "The Writer in Totalitarian Countries" II, 6-Feb-85; cuid4341; 180939 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Breyten Breytenbach "The Writer in Totalitarian Countries" III, 6-Feb-85; cuid4342; 180940 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Times Square Conference I, 26-Oct-90; cuid4343; 180894 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Times Square Conference II, 26-10-90; cuid4344; 180895 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Times Square Conference III, 26-Oct-90; cuid4345; 180896 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Russian Cons Eve I, 21-Mar-91; cuid4346; 180897 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Russian Cons Eve II, 21-Mar-91; cuid4347; 180898 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - AM I, 21-Mar-91; cuid4348; 180899 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - AM II, 21-Mar-91; cuid4349; 180900 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - AM III, 21-Mar-91; cuid4350; 180901 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Glasnost PM I, 21-Mar-1991; cuid4351; 180902 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Glasnost PM II, 21-Mar-91; cuid4352; 180903 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Morning I, 22-Mar-91; cuid4353; 180904 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Morning II, 22-Mar-91; cuid4354; 180905 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - PM I, 22-Mar-91; cuid4355; 180906 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - PM II, 22-Mar-91; cuid4356; 180907 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Glasnost AM I, 22-Mar-91; cuid4357; 180908 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Glasnost Eve I, 22-Mar-91; cuid4358; 180910 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Glasnost AM II, 22-Mar-91; cuid4359; 180909 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Glasnost Eve II, 22-Mar-91; cuid4360; 180911 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Subseries C: Mini Disks, 181007
    - Greenblatt, 1-Oct-04; cuid4361; 181008 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Canall, 22-Oct-04; cuid4362; 181009 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Nafisi, 3-Dec-04; cuid4363; 181010 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Pete Hamill, Undated; cuid4364; 181011 (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Frazier, Undated; cuid4365; 181012 (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Election, Undated; cuid4366; 181013 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Post Election, Undated; cuid4367; 181015 (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Satrapi, Undated; cuid4368; 181016 (Box 76, Folder 31)
    - Undefined (Label "Rachel Cohen" has beencrossed out), Undated; cuid4369; 181017 (Box 76, Folder 32)